<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Brad Parbs</title>
    <link>https://bradparbs.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Brad Parbs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 00:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bradparbs.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hey, hey, hey, it&#39;s a new site!</title>
      <link>https://bradparbs.com/2020/hey-hey-hey-its-a-new-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradparbs.com/2020/hey-hey-hey-its-a-new-site/</guid>
      <description>After a few years of barely changing anything on my site, I&amp;rsquo;m super happy to finally build a whole new site! 🎉
This site is powered by Hugo &amp;amp; Tailwind CSS. It&amp;rsquo;s been super fun to build, and I&amp;rsquo;m excited to finally get back to writing some blog posts.
I&amp;rsquo;ve recently been updating a few of my other sites, and it feels good to use some sleek new tools to do it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Beginner’s Guide to the Best Command Line Tools</title>
      <link>https://bradparbs.com/2015/a-beginners-guide-to-the-best-command-line-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradparbs.com/2015/a-beginners-guide-to-the-best-command-line-tools/</guid>
      <description>As someone who loves the command line, I’m always striving to make my workflow easier, more efficient, and just overall better. Hopefully, by walking through my set up and my recommendations for the best command line tools, you’ll find some nifty tips and tricks you can adapt to make your workflow better too.
The command line is a scary place if you’ve never been there before. It is. You can do some really powerful and dangerous things to your computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started with Vagrant &amp; VVV for local development</title>
      <link>https://bradparbs.com/2015/getting-started-with-vagrant-vvv-for-local-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradparbs.com/2015/getting-started-with-vagrant-vvv-for-local-development/</guid>
      <description>When I started doing web development, I think I started the way a lot of us did. You have a site you want to work on, so you connect with FTP, download a file, modify it, upload it back up, and then refresh the page to see if your changes worked. This process doesn’t really work when you’re working with a team of people, or on a site that people are actively going to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up WordPress &#43; Nginx &#43; HHVM For The Fastest Possible Load Times</title>
      <link>https://bradparbs.com/2014/setting-up-wordpress-nginx-hhvm-for-the-fastest-possible-load-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradparbs.com/2014/setting-up-wordpress-nginx-hhvm-for-the-fastest-possible-load-times/</guid>
      <description>One of the most enjoyable parts about writing code is writing efficient and performant functionality. No matter how fast your code is, if your server itself isn’t running to it’s maximum performance, you’re not delivering your site as fast as you could be. By setting up Nginx and the new HHVM, you can get your server delivering fully loaded pages faster than most servers answer a request.
HHVM is an open-source virtual machine designed for executing programs written in Hackand PHP.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
