<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Brad Parbs</title>
    <link>https://bradparbs.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Brad Parbs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2015 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bradparbs.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://bradparbs.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradparbs.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>There are plenty of ways to contact &amp;amp; follow me. I currently use Github , Twitter , and LinkedIn . And of course, you can always Email me .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://bradparbs.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradparbs.com/projects/</guid>
      <description>Tools / Software  vv - The best tool for managing Varying Vagrant Vagrants sites. Worndpress - The best fork of WordPress. my dotfiles - My way-too-documented dotfiles. VVV Provision Flipper - Toggle between different VVV provisioning scripts. v - Wrapper for vv - half as long a command, only works half the time. t - a super simple cli todo manager. WP-CLI Examples - An example of a WP-CLI script to start from.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Beginner’s Guide to the Best Command Line Tools</title>
      <link>https://bradparbs.com/2015/a-beginners-guide-to-the-best-command-line-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradparbs.com/2015/a-beginners-guide-to-the-best-command-line-tools/</guid>
      <description>As someone who loves the command line, I’m always striving to make my workflow easier, more efficient, and just overall better. Hopefully, by walking through my set up and my recommendations for the best command line tools, you’ll find some nifty tips and tricks you can adapt to make your workflow better too.
The command line is a scary place if you’ve never been there before. It is. You can do some really powerful and dangerous things to your computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started with Vagrant &amp; VVV for local development</title>
      <link>https://bradparbs.com/2015/getting-started-with-vagrant-vvv-for-local-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradparbs.com/2015/getting-started-with-vagrant-vvv-for-local-development/</guid>
      <description>When I started doing web development, I think I started the way a lot of us did. You have a site you want to work on, so you connect with FTP, download a file, modify it, upload it back up, and then refresh the page to see if your changes worked. This process doesn’t really work when you’re working with a team of people, or on a site that people are actively going to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up WordPress &#43; Nginx &#43; HHVM For The Fastest Possible Load Times</title>
      <link>https://bradparbs.com/2014/setting-up-wordpress-nginx-hhvm-for-the-fastest-possible-load-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradparbs.com/2014/setting-up-wordpress-nginx-hhvm-for-the-fastest-possible-load-times/</guid>
      <description>One of the most enjoyable parts about writing code is writing efficient and performant functionality. No matter how fast your code is, if your server itself isn’t running to it’s maximum performance, you’re not delivering your site as fast as you could be. By setting up Nginx and the new HHVM , you can get your server delivering fully loaded pages faster than most servers answer a request.
HHVM is an open-source virtual machine designed for executing programs written in Hackand PHP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://bradparbs.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradparbs.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I’m currently a Developer at Awesome Motive , where I am building the easiest WordPress form plugin: WPForms .
I like to build things on the internet.
I’m a WordPress fanatic. I’ve contributed to WordPress Core, have built a variety of custom plugins &amp;amp; themes, as well as a variety of tools and guides.
I have spoken at WordCamps across the United States, as well as many local meetups in Milwaukee and Chicago.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
